Do you want me to know what
you
want?
I'm Tentakushin wa Dede hitotsu dei Kocoro
kara hold up Raise your
hands Kukukuku naai
Raise your hands Melia te de fangai Raise
your hands Mou yikai
Raise your hands Iiisakai
Omoshiroi desu I love you
I misjudged you.
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me.
I'm talking about Claire.
She cried all day yesterday.
I'm leaving Miss Claire
to you now, Princess.
Please take care of her.
I'm sure she'll be lonely.
Because of you!
Maybe so, but I still lost our duel.
And I quit as her maid, so there's
nothing I can do for her now.
You're really giving up just like that?
Did you ever even love
her in the first place?
Who do you think you are asking me that?
You're the one who started all this.
You took Miss Claire away from me.
You turned tail and ran.
I'm just your excuse.
You were always going to give up on her.
What do you mean I was always...
Did you really think
I'd buy your little act?
I don't expect her to return my feelings.
I'm putting her happiness first.
Those are lies you tell
to protect yourself.
The truth is you're terrified
of her rejecting you.
So you run and hide and you pretend
it's all for her sake. You're wrong!
No, she's right.
I don't care if my love is unrequited.
That's a lie. I do.
I do.
The truth is...
I want her to love me back.
Look, I want to be hers,
and I want her to be mine.
I want it so much, and yet...
I'm not stupid enough
to indulge in a fantasy.
We can't be together.
We're both girls, and she's
in love with someone else.
So you just cut and run, then?
You think you'll be happy keeping
up this farce and not even trying?
I've made it this far, right?
I can swallow my feelings because
it's what's best for Miss Claire!
You're a fool.
Relationships like that
are doomed to fail.
I know better than anyone,
because it happened to me.
There was someone whom I
loved with all my heart,
just as you love Claire with all of yours.
I told myself I was fine
so long as she was happy,
even if we didn't end up together.
I shoved my feelings down until
I couldn't contain them anymore.
Then I made a terrible mistake.
Considering the difference
in our statuses she
would never have turned
me down even still i
Before long she vanished from the
palace and i never saw her again
Feelings that seek nothing
in return will always
become twisted the heart
isn't strong or pure
Enough to withstand them
what happened changed me
i started going to brothels
and disguise Otherwise,
I thought keeping relationships
transactional would prevent heartache,
for them and for me.
But I never felt fulfilled.
I wish I could take it back,
but I can't. It's too late.
She's gone.
I don't understand what you want me to do.
If you're still determined
to give up on Claire,
then I think I'll use her for my
amusement just like the others.
You wouldn't please tell
me you're not serious?
I'll have so much fun corrupting her!
I won't let You do that!
Really, what's your big plan?
The scales at
the amor ceremony,
measuring your feelings
on The scales of love!
It's rather bold, I must admit.
But in case you've forgotten, you
lost and Claire Is already mine!
I won't accept this challenge unless
there's something in it for me.
If I win,
You'll be mine as well!
That's my condition!
Fine by me!
I won't lose!
That's the spirit!
I like the fire in your eyes!
I have to win!
I can't let her take Miss Claire?
A challenge?
At the Amor Ceremony?
Again, i wasn't consulted.
We had no choice.
You still won't tell us what you
want, so now it's come to this!
Tell me something, claire?
Have you ever wondered whose feelings were
really first measured
on the scales of love?
Was it the two suitors
whose love God tested?
Or was it someone else?
Unbelievable!
The audacity of those two!
My feelings are not pawns in a game!
If you're looking for Rey, she's not here.
I would imagine she's out on a job.
A job?
She's been accepting every monster hunting
quest on the Knights bulletin board
She's taking them all what in
the world could she be thinking?
Another stupid magic stone.
Guess I shouldn't be surprised with the
measly drop rate like point five percent.
Stay focused.
I don't have time to wallow in my misery.
I know full well Princess
Manaria is capable of anything,
even getting her hands
on a flower of flora.
This is my only chance at winning!
I won't give up!
I told myself I could
never use my knowledge
of the game to my advantage romantically.
That was my rule.
I thought it would be unfair
to use the circumstances
of my reincarnation to
win Miss Claire's heart.
But I was wrong from the start.
But if I want a future with Miss Claire,
if a happy ending with her
means more to me than anything,
then it doesn't matter
what anyone else thinks.
Almost time.
I need to hurry up.
Worry not, friend.
No way I'm giving up that easily.
Relay air!
Bicycle wave!
Stone pinning!
Imagine if you could
just press reset on love.
Life would be easier.
But there's no going back.
I love her too much.
Please, Ms.
Clare, wait for me.
This year's Amour ceremony
seems to be a success.
So who are you hoping
will win in your match?
Rey or Princess Manaria?
As if it even matters.
I don't concern myself with fools who
would treat me like some sort of trophy.
Well, I'm a bit biased,
but I hope Rey wins.
So you're taking her side
because she's your friend then?
That's not the only reason.
Tell me something.
How do you really feel about Rey?
How do I...
Please, tell me the truth.
There's nothing for me to tell.
The commoner is...
Well, she's absurd.
She's done nothing but spout
nonsense since the moment we met.
She tricked my father to become my maid,
and she's been driving me mad
with her teasing ever since.
She is utterly
incorrigible, reprehensible.
That girl is simply the cheekiest
commoner I have ever known.
Well, look at that.
It's nice to see a smile on your face.
Miss Claire,
if Rey does win this, will you give her
another chance to serve as your maid?
I cannot.
You must understand.
I am a noble.
One such as I could never deign
to beg a commoner to be my maid.
It is completely out of the question.
Then that's that.
We'll blame nobility.
It's a heavy burden to bear.
I suppose I'll just have
to hope for a miracle.
A miracle? Yes.
One that makes everything
work out in the end,
like in the fairy tales
we read as children.
Hello, sister.
Claire, this is for you.
Isn't that flower a...
Yes, it's a flower of flora.
Where's Rei?
I see.
Then I deliver this poem to you, my dear.
My love has placed her faith in
me, and I shall never reject her.
I swear to you here and now, that
I will always be your protector.
The same words she said
when we were young.
Stop right there!
Ray!
Wait, what happened?
Why are you so disheveled?
Well, well.
Looks like you didn't run away after all.
Why would I run away?
Taking your butt is my
number one priority.
Don't worry, Miss Claire.
It's going to be okay.
I promise I won't let her have you.
You poor naive thing
you've shown up just to
lose again I have a
flower of Flora after all.
There's no greater offering in the
world but do entertain me with yours!
Go on my offering
is this huh a twin.
This must be some kind of joke that's
for the scales of love to decide?
Very well, then.
I'll go first.
I offer the truth of my heart,
presented for God's judgment.
Look at that.
There's no way Ray can win.
What was she thinking?
She was doomed from the start.
My turn.
That isn't even close to
good enough. It's all over.
Will you have faith in Rey?
Seems that the win is still mine.
How did...
Look at the scales!
The flower floor really lost? But how?
It was nothing.
A twig.
It's more than that. Much more.
The Branch of Eternal Love is a rare item
dropped by a monster
called the Entwined Tree.
Offering it unlocks an exclusive cutscene.
It's a secret to all
but the most hardcore.
I thought the Flower of Flora was the
best possible offering someone could give.
To be fair, it was the best offering known
to date, so kudos on tracking it down.
but I was able to find something
even better than the best.
Well, you can't say I
didn't warn you, Manaria.
Rey's not someone you
should ever underestimate.
Listen, Miss Claire.
I'm not perfect.
I make jokes to hide how I feel,
and I can't give you a
grand fairy tale romance.
But whether the scales of love
or even God acknowledges it,
I love you with all my heart.
I am yours.
Nothing will ever change that.
I love you, and I will
until my last breath.
So please, I want to be with you, not as
your maid or servant, but as your partner.
You're unbelievable.
Well, looks like I lost
this one fair and square.
Ray, you really are one
of a kind, you know.
What's the meaning of this?
Have you lost your mind, sister?
I'm sorry, Claire.
But to tell you the truth, I've been
after Ray from the very beginning.
Wait, so you weren't trying to steal Ms.
Claire?
You were messing with me?
That's right.
The look on your face was so
adorable, I couldn't help myself.
What is that?
Get away from me, you freak!
This is exactly what I mean.
You're so cute when you're angry.
It just makes me want you even more.
Stop it!
Gray is mine and I won't let you
take her from me, do you understand?
Huh?
Um, care to repeat that?
Uh, no, is it?
Uh, no!
You said I knew!
I ordered you to get out of yourself!
We are in a very public space!
No can do, my love cup rendezvous!
Over Miss Claire!
Shots are not you fools!
All this behavior is undignified!
What does this mean we'll
be together forever now?
Well, that was certainly
an unexpected development.
Princess Manaria, forgive my impudence,
but this contest has been decided.
Indeed it has.
Oh, I love you too, Remy!
Thank you.
Thank you so much
for
joining us.
Thank you.
I don't understand.
Why are you returning to Seuss so soon?
Forgive me, but the First
Prince passed away suddenly.
Now the rite of succession
has been moved up,
so I'm afraid I need to return
to my family's dreadful feud.
Besides, Rey shot me down.
What better way to recover
than a fight for the throne?
But mark my words, I'll come back
to bother you when it's done.
Or you could not.
Enough, Rey.
You're being very rude.
I won't soon forget how much
fun I had with all of you.
Neither will I.
Get gone, bewitch.
You really did put your
foot where your mouth is?
Serves you right.
Show some respect.
That is not the proper
way to treat a princess.
Oh, believe me, I know.
I'm just saving the princess
treatment for my princess.
Well, you look at that.
You two are closer than two peas in a pod.
I'm too effective for my own good.
Come to think of it, I wonder
if that was her goal all along.
Is it possible that she
played the bad guy the whole
time just to push Miss Claire
and me closer together?
Hold the phone!
Even if that's true, there must have
been a more painless way to go about it!
Quick request.
Mind if I borrow Ray just one last time?
Farewell!
And like a gust of
wind, she came and went.
Now that that's over with.
Congratulations to you, Miss Claire!
All that matters is that
Miss Claire is happy.
Please don't cry, Loretta.
At least we still love each other!
True love takes many forms.
You love birds have our full support.
Wait just a moment.
What in the world are
you all talking about?
We're talking about you and Ray Aren't
you two gonna invite us to your wedding?
Are you?
Our wedding?
Me, Claire Francois, a commoner's bride No,
I think I'd prefer to call Rey my bride.
Wait.
I take it back!
Rey, I must ask you something.
Sure, ask away.
Who are you, really?
You knew of a secret offering that
surpassed the flower of Flora.
And I hear you neutralized an unknown
poison from the Nur Empire as well.
Where did you acquire that knowledge?
I can't tell you.
Are you a spy sent by the Empire? I'm not.
Do you swear?
I swear to Miss Claire.
It's true.
My only allegiance is to Miss Claire.
And my only mission is to stop the
tragedy that awaits in her future.
You swear to miss Claire huh?
Well, coming from you that means
more than an oath to God ever.
possibly could.
Will you promise to look
after Claire for me?
It's as good as done.
Say it again, pretty please.
We still go as quick as I tap.
What are you talking about?
You know what I mean.
Tell me more about how I'm yours.
You're getting ahead of yourself again,
Ray after all we just started
you
know you
started calling me by my
name and what if I did
Famous Claire I love you
I couldn't quite hear that
I'm in love with you and
I don't care who knows it
I love you.
How many times do I have to explain?
Help me, buddy.
This is my way for you.
Shame, woman.
Give me your points out.
Oh, no. No, please.
It's crazy.
People are scary.
I love you.